http://www.jewettmachine.com/privacy.html

Phone: 804.233.9873  |  E-mail: info@jewettmachine.com
Home |  About Jewett Machine |  Tour the Shop |  Case Studies |  Contact Us |  RFQ |  Site Map
Privacy Policy
Jewett Machine respects your privacy and the purpose for which our site visitors provide us information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.
Information CollectedIf you request or submit information to Jewett Machine by sending an e-mail via the "mail to:" function or filling out a "request for information" form, we may save your e-mail address as well as any other information you may provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, e-mail, or phone to convey information about Jewett Machine solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your e-mail and other information you provide will not be sold to any third party.
Information Collected by OthersThis notice addresses only the policy of Jewett Machine website and not the sites that users access via links from our site. Jewett Machine is not responsible for the information collection policies of other sites, nor for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, nor for the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.
Cookies Jewett Machine website does not use cookies.
Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal InformationIf you would like to have your personal information removed from Jewett Machine please send an e-mail via the feedback form, with "Remove personal information" in the subject line. To update, change, or correct your personal information, please send an e-mail via the feedback form with the appropriate changes.
Legally Compelled Disclosure of InformationJewett Machine may disclose information when legally compelled to do so; in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.
Periodic Policy ChangesPlease note that Jewett Machine reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.
This policy statement is made in the name of Jewett Machine and is effective as of may 5, 2008. This statement does not create an agreement between Jewett Machine and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.
For inquiries contact:Jewett Machine 2901 Maury Street. Richmond, VA 23224Phone: 804.233.9873Fax: 804.230.4473E-mail: info@jewettmachine
Jewett Machine  |  2901 Maury Street. Richmond, VA 23224  |  Phone: 804.233.9873  |  Fax: 804.230.4473  |  E-Mail: info@jewettmachine  |  Privacy Policy
Site created by ThomasNet Web Solutions, a division of ThomasNet.com
